Brett Schanzenbach

Vista, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Brett-Schanzenbach/6740c6329fa5c112

I am a game designer and animator who specializes in character design and gameplay. I have been a project manager on game and animation projects, and have experience working as part of a team.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Animation Dev Assistant

Rockstar Games - Carlsbad, CA - April 2017 to July 2017

Animation assistant tasked with reviewing, and supplying assets, for animated cutscenes and in game scenes. Worked with MotionBuilder and 3DS Max to update characters and props and make sure they are working properly in game. Also performed set captures and prop placement for animated characters and assets.

QA Tester

Activision - Edina, MN - July 2016 to November 2016

Quality Assurance tester for Call of Duty®: Infinite Warfare

Storyboard Artist

Baby Rascal - Edina, MN - January 2015 to May 2015

Lead storyboard artist for a short film project titled "baby rascal".

Technical Director

Swing Set Games - Edina, MN - June 2014 to May 2015

Lead asset manager of game assets for the Unity game engine for use on OUYA.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Applied Science in Business

Minneapolis Media Institute 2015

Associate of Applied Science in Art & Animation

Minneapolis Media Institute 2014

Associate of Fine Arts in Fine Arts

Normandale Community College 2010

SKILLS

Unity 3D (3 years), Autodesk Maya (3 years), Adobe (5 years), Blender3D (2 years), Autodesk Motion Builder (2 years)

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/brett-schanzenbach-511b9667

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCeAXxteRIIGLw6rpacZaxaw

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Javascript, C#, Python Languages
- Unity Game Engine, Monodevelop, Adobe CC, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Premiere Software

Pro, Blender, Autodesk Maya, MotionBuilder, Mudbox, Zbrush